Let The Evil Out
The Dare is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Giles Alderson.
A rare family night for Jay takes a brutal twist when he
awakens in a basement with three other prisoners.
As their vengeful captor runs riot, Jay engages in a twisted battle to
solve the puzzle to his past and save his family's future.
Jay Jackson, played by Bart Edwards.
Credence, played by Richard Brake.
Adam Heinz, played by Richard Short.
Kat Gill, played by Alexandra Evans.
Dominic Craven, played by Robert Maaser.
Teen Dominic Craven, played by Harry Jarvis.
The Dare is a 2019 horror film directed by Giles Alderson starring Bart Edwards,
Richard Brake, Richard Short, Alexandra Evans, and Robert Maaser.
The film explores themes of prisoner, affectation, puzzle, survival, torture.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.